Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): Bargaining--Petitions (Local 215), Undated; cuid6795 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6796 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1949-1958; cuid6797 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1973; cuid6798 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Includes Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)), 1975-1985; cuid6799 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Includes Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)), 1985-2001; cuid6800 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)) (I), 1993-1994; cuid6801 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)) (II), 1993-1994; cuid6802 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1999; cuid6803 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): DC 1707 Staff Representatives Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6804 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Grievances (Local 215), 1963-1995; cuid6805 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Care Services of Long Island, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 389), 1988-2000; cuid6806 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-2000; cuid6807 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6808 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): Grievance (Local 215), 1980; cuid6809 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Jewish Community Center of Metropolitan New Jersey/United Jewish Centers of MetroWest: Grievance--Arlene Safft (Local 215), 1994-1995; cuid6810 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1995; cuid6811 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1996-1999; cuid6812 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1996-2000; cuid6813 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 107), 1995-2000; cuid6814 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances (Local 107), 1998-2000; cuid6815 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances (Local 107), 2000-2001; cuid6816 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances--Madeleine Fante (Local 107), 1998-2000; cuid6817 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances--re: Health Insurance Benefits (Local 107), 1998-2000; cuid6818 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community Federation of Metropolitan New Jersey: Bargaining (Local 215), [1982]; cuid6819 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-2000; cuid6820 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Sofia Kabak (I) (Local 215), 1996-1998; cuid6821 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Sofia Kabak (II) (Local 215), 1996-1998; cuid6822 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Craig Wasserberg (Local 215), 1999-2000; cuid6823 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Community Services of Long Island: Bargaining (Local 215), 1980; cuid6824 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Council for Public Affairs (JCPA)[formerly National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Bargaining (Local 107), 1984-2000; cuid6825 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Council for Public Affairs (JCPA)[formerly National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Elections (Local 107), 1984; cuid6826 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1954-1958; cuid6827 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1964; cuid6828 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1966-1976; cuid6829 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Family Service: Grievances (Local 215), 1956-1961; cuid6830 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Family Service: Grievances (Local 215), 1961-1974; cuid6831 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1947-1967; cuid6832 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1970-1989; cuid6833 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1989-2001; cuid6834 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Jewish National Fund: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 107), 1995-2000; cuid6835 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6836 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Job Corps: General Administrative, 1998; cuid6837 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Joint Purchasing Corporation: Bargaining, 1995; cuid6838 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Kings Bay YM and YWHA: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1996; cuid6839 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Kings Bay YM and YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid6840 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Leake and Watts: General Administrative, 1998; cuid6841 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Little Flower Children's Services: Bargaining, Grievance, General Adminstrative (Local 215), 1995-1999; cuid6842 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Living Resources Corporation: Election Petition, NLRB, 2000; cuid6843 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, Inc.: Bargaining, 1992; cuid6844 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Long Island Women's Coalition: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6845 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1964; cuid6846 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1967-1985; cuid6847 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1987-1991; cuid6848 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1992-2004; cuid6849 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Louise Wise Services: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6850 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Louise Wise Services: General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid6851 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid6852 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1998; cuid6853 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1997-1999; cuid6854 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Idriys Muhammad (Local 215), 1998; cuid6855 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Sam Shortte (Local 215), 1996-2000; cuid6856 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Raquel Vasquez (Local 215), 1997-1999; cuid6857 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lucille Murray Child Development: Grievances (Local 205), 1989; cuid6858 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Marriott Management Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6859 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Metro Care Home Services: Unfair Labor Practices, 1999; cuid6860 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Metro North Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1989; cuid6861 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miricle Makers, Inc.: NLRB Petition, Election Materials, 1998-1999, undated; cuid6862 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mobilization for Youth: Bargaining, 1964-1965; cuid6863 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Mobilization for Youth: Bargaining, 1966-1974; cuid6864 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Bargaining, DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1991-1996; cuid6865 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999; cuid6866 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Grievances (Local 215), 1988, 1992-1996; cuid6867 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1951-1969; cuid6868 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1984; cuid6869 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1986-1996; cuid6870 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1999; cuid6871 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Grievance (Local 107), 2001; cuid6872 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Board of the YMCA: Bargaining (Local 107), 1995; cuid6873 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1968; cuid6874 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - National Committee for Labor Israel: Bargaining (Local 107), 1972-1992; cuid6875 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Bargaining (Local 107), 1994-1995; cuid6876 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Bargaining (Local 107), 1997-2000; cuid6877 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 107), 1995-1997; cuid6878 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Grievances/Personnel Issues (Local 107), 1991-1996; cuid6879 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - National Council of Jewish Women: Personnel (Local 107), 1994-1997; cuid6880 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995; cuid6881 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - New Jersey Federation Agencies: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, 1995-1996; cuid6882 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Arbitration, NLRB, 2003-2004; cuid6883 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1990; cuid6884 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1991; cuid6885 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 215), 1994-1995; cuid6886 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6887 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Negotiations (Local 215), 1999-2003; cuid6888 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining (Local 215), 2000-2001; cuid6889 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Arbitration (Local 215), 2003; cuid6890 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Bargaining--Retrenchment/Layoffs (Local 215), 2003; cuid6891 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 1971; cuid6892 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-2003, undated; cuid6893 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative (Local 215), 2003; cuid6894 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): General Administrative--Comptroller NYC and NYS (Local 215), 2003-2004; cuid6895 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances/Personnel (Local 215), 1999; cuid6896 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances (Local 215), 1998-2003; cuid6897 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievances--Work Load (Local 215), 1992-1993; cuid6898 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Rose Levy (Local 215), 1996; cuid6899 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Irma Logas (Local 215), 1993-1994; cuid6900 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Grievance--Farshad Yeroshalmi (Local 215), 1993; cuid6901 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Conflict of Internet Policy (Local 215), 2002; cuid6902 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Health Benefits (Local 215), 1996-2000; cuid6903 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Job Descriptions (Local 215), 1994-2001, undated; cuid6904 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Job Specialists (Local 215), 1999-2003; cuid6905 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Layoffs/Bumping/Retrenchment (Local 215), 2003; cuid6906 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Daniel O'Sullivan (Local 215), 1998-2001; cuid6907 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Sabbath Observance (Local 215), 2002; cuid6908 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Staff Directory (Local 215), 1997-1998; cuid6909 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - New York Association for New Americans (NYANA): Personnel--Voluntary Retrenchment/Furlough (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6910 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 1996-1999; cuid6911 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 2000-2001; cuid6912 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - New York City--Administration for Children's Services: Bargaining, 2002; cuid6913 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1991-1996; cuid6914 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1994-1996; cuid6915 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - New York City--Brooklyn Bureau of Community Services: Bargaining, 1997-2002; cuid6916 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - New York Society for the Deaf: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1999; cuid6917 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - New York State Association for Retarded Citizens: Bargaining (Local 253), 1992-1995; cuid6918 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1952-1963; cuid6919 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-1971; cuid6920 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975-1980; cuid6921 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1994; cuid6922 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1998-2004; cuid6923 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6924 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 92nd Street YM and YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1970, 1992; cuid6925 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: Bargaining, 1991-1994; cuid6926 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: Bargaining, 1996-1999, undated; cuid6927 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), Local 153: General Administrative, 1997-1999, undated; cuid6928 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1990; cuid6929 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: DC 1707 Staff Representive Files (Local 215), 1995-1996; cuid6930 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Paul J. Cooper Center for Human Services: Grievance (Local 215), 1995; cuid6931 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Pomonok Home Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001; cuid6932 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Pomonok Home Services: Grievances (Local 389), 1998-2000; cuid6933 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1956-1976; cuid6934 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1978-1981; cuid6935 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1983-1987; cuid6936 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1989-1991; cuid6937 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1993-1998; cuid6938 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: Bargaining (Local 253), 1999-[2005]; cuid6939 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Postgraduate Center for Mental Health: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6940 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Quo Vadis Montessori Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1988; cuid6941 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997; cuid6942 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1996; cuid6943 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Richard G. Rosenthal YM and YWHA of Northern Westchester: Personnel (Local 215), 1995-1998; cuid6944 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1963; cuid6945 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-1975; cuid6946 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), [1979]-1992; cuid6947 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1994-1996; cuid6948 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1996-2000; cuid6949 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Grievances--Unfair Labor Practices Case (Local 215), 1999-2000; cuid6950 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Riverdale YM - YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6951 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Rockland ARC: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997; cuid6952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1997; cuid6953 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1995; cuid6954 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Samuel Field - Bay Terrace YM and YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000; cuid6955 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Selfhelp Community Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1993-2001; cuid6956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Selfhelp Community Services: General Administrative (Local 389), 1990-2000; cuid6957 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Services for the Aged: Grievances, General Administrative (Local 389), 1986-1989; cuid6958 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1951-1959; cuid6959 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1961-1971; cuid6960 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1973-1979; cuid6961 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1986; cuid6962 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1985-1989; cuid6963 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1989-1992; cuid6964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1993-2000; cuid6965 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Sheltering Arms Childrens Service: Grievance (Local 215), 1995; cuid6966 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1981-2003, undated; cuid6967 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1997-2002; cuid6968 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 1998-2002; cuid6969 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--Management Proposals (Local 253), 1999-2003; cuid6970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--DC 1707 Contract Proposals (Local 253), 2001. undated; cuid6971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining--Contract Amendment Votes (Local 253), 2000, undated; cuid6972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Shield Institute: Bargaining (Local 253), 2001-2003; cuid6973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Audits, Clinics (Local 253), 1998-2001; cuid6974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) (Local 253), 1999-2000; cuid6975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--DC 1707 Health and Insurance Fund (Local 253), 2000; cuid6976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Directions (Local 253), 2000-2001, undated; cuid6977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Dues (Local 253), 2001-2005; cuid6978 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Excessive Teacher Turnover Prevention Program (Local 253), 2001-2003; cuid6979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Labor Management Committee (Local 253), 2002-2004; cuid6980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Meetings (Local 253), 2000-2001; cuid6981 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Office of Mental Retardation and Developmental Disablilities (OMRDD) (Local 253), 2001, undated; cuid6982 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Safety and Security (Local 253), 2005; cuid6983 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Shield Institute: General Administrative--Union Demonstrations (Local 253), 2002; cuid6984 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 1996; cuid6985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2000-2004; cuid6986 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2000-2005; cuid6987 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances (Local 253), 2003-2005; cuid6988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances, Class Action (Local 253), 2001-2003; cuid6989 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances/Personnel (Local 253), 2003-2005; cuid6990 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Sharon David (Local 253), 1999-2005; cuid6991 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Mary Leto (Local 253), 2001-2002; cuid6992 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--James McCarther (Local 253), 2001-2002; cuid6993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--A-K (Local 253), 2000-2003; cuid6994 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--L-Mc (Local 253), 2000-2004; cuid6995 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Shield Institute: Grievances--Me-Z (Local 253), 2000-2004; cuid6996 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Certification/Temporary Licenses (Local 253), 2001-2003; cuid6997 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Certification/Uncertified Teachers (Local 253), 2003-2004; cuid6998 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Employee Files (Local 253), 2000-2004; cuid6999 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Shield Institute: Personnel--Employee Handbook (Local 253), 1998; cuid7000 (Box 31, Folder 5)